Guide to the Kathe Burkhart Papers MSS.467
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III. Writing, 1983-2014; 7.17 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes, 1 record carton, 1 flat box, and 1 oversize flat box.; 485 Megabytes in 351 computer files.; 4 audiocassettes; 1 videocassettes (vhs)
  This series contains material related to Burhart's poems, haikus, short stories, articles, and novels. Files in this series include short published pieces, work files for novels, and recordings of readings and performances. Drafts, notes, and published versions of poems, haikus, short stories, as well as review articles by Burkhart are also in this series. A significant amount of the paper and electronic files in this series pertain to the creation of various Burkhart books, including From Under the 8-Ball (published in 1985), The Double Standard (published in 2002 and 2005), The Double Standard (published in 2005), and Dudes (published in 2014). These files contain drafts, research, page and cover layouts, and correspondence with publishers, agents, and friends. Burkhart's 2006 novel Between the Lines was inspired by letters sent to her Aunt Grace Knipe from her friend Kate Gibson. Paper and electronic files related to the writing and publishing of this novel include research, drafts, page layouts, and correspondence. The original letters are in Series VII.
  - "Feminism in the Art School?" in the WALT CalArts Publication, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Lace Book Store -- Budget, Supply List, Business Plan, 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Reviews Written by Burkhart, 1984-1986, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Readings and Related Events -- Promotional Material, 1984-1998, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - "I Had a Dream" in Hudson Center Journal, December 1985 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Kathe Burkhart -- "On the Dole", 1985 (Box 45, Audiocassette 467.0005)
  - Kathe Burkhart -- "On the Dole", 1985 (Box 45, Audiocassette 467.0006)
  - High Performance Magazine -- Writer Guidelines, Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - From Under the 8-Ball (1985) -- Edited Typescripts, Funding, Page Proof Layouts, circa 1985 (Box 19, Folder 1-5)
  - From Under the 8-Ball (1985) -- Excerpt and Cover Layout, 1985-1986 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - From Under the 8-Ball (1985) -- Cover Image, circa 1985
  - Correspondence, 1985-2014 (Box 19, Folder 6-9)
  - "Everyman" in New Leaves Review, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Untitled Poem in National Poetry Magazine of the Lower East Side, February 1986 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - "Prescriptive" in New Leaves Review, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - "The Milk Truck" in Farm and Alternator Magazine, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 13, Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Burkhart Books and Readings -- Articles and Reviews, 1988-2006 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Collection of Poems-- Typescripts, circa 1985-1991 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Theatrical Piece -- Jail of Gender -- Program, Script, Promotional Material, Layout, circa 1990s (Box 20, Folder 4, Box 27, Folder 2)
  - "The Broken Record" in Slut Magazine, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Reading at Feature Gallery, 1991 (Box 45, Audiocassette 467.0007)
  - Reading / Spoken Word Performance at Feature Gallery, 1992 (Box 45, Audiocassette 467.0008)
  - Bomb Magazine, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - "Bobby's Fluff" Published in Promotional Copy, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Zapp Magazine on Video -- Features Burkhart's Piece, "Bobby's Fluff", March 1994 (Box 45, Vhs 467.0018)
  - Short Stories and Other Writings, 1994-2013
  - Poems, 1994-2014
  - Poetry -- Typescripts, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Haikus, 1995-2012
  - Ex Patriote: Some Journal Selections by Kathe Burkhart, 1996
  - Short Story -- "Beffe van de Pijp", 1996, 2006, 2013
  - Art Kitchen Magazine -- Writing and Art Contributions, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Literary Submissions -- Notes, Lists, 1999-2004, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Address and Mailing Lists, 1999-2007 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Short Story -- "Close Calls", 2000, 2003, 2013
  - World Trade Center Haikus, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Articles, 2002-2011
  - NYFA Funding -- Application Materials, circa 2002 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Book Printer Companies -- Notes, Invoices, Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - The Double Standard (2005) -- Excerpts, Edited Typescripts and Drafts, 1991-2005 (Box 20, Folder 12-13, Box 21, Folder 1-6)
  - The Double Standard (2005) -- Typescripts for Chapters, 1994-2008
  - The Double Standard (2005) -- Translator Notes, Publishing Contracts, Page Layout Samples and Proofs, Book, Event Publicity, 1998-2007 (Box 21, Folder 7-12, Box 22, Folder 1-6)
  - Kathe Burkhart: Bad Girl: Works from 1983-2000 (2005) -- Cover Art, Description, and Book, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Between the Lines (2006) -- Notes, Research, Copies of Photographs, Publishing Contracts, Correspondence, 2002-2004, undated (Box 22, Folder 7-13)
  - Between the Lines (2006) -- Early First Draft, Edited Typescripts, circa 2005 (Box 22, Folder 14, Box 23, Folder 1-9, Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Between the Lines (2006) -- Translations of French Reviews, Royalty Documentation, 2006-2008 (Box 24, Folder 2-3)
  - Between the Lines (2006) -- Book Proof Layout, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Between the Lines (2006) -- Research-Related, Grant Applications, and Correspondence, 2000-2013
  - Short Story -- "Cells and the City" in Word For it: A Literary Review, circa 2005 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Kathe Burkhart. The Liz Taylor Series: The First 25 Years, 1982-2007 (2007) -- Press Release, Cover Design
  - "Famous for 15 Seconds", 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - "Fair Ground" -- Edited Typescripts, circa 2008 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Reading at Crossing Border -- Image, 2009
  - Emotional Weather -- Typescript, 2009, 2011
  - Dudes (2014) -- Edited Typescripts, Drafts, Grant Applications, 1993-2014 (Box 24, Folder 8-13, Box 25, Folder 1-4, Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Dudes (2014) -- Typescripts of Chapters, 1994-2014
  - Untitled Writing, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - "Excerpts from the Diary of a Teenage Girl in the Seventies" -- Drafts, Published version in Total Metal, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Notes, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - "Mandy and Me", undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Series IV. Graphic Design, 1981-2005; 6.84 Linear Feet in 2 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes, and 2 oversize flat boxes.
  Burkhart has worked as a graphic designer for clients including American Express, Coach, and Dutch East India Trading / Homestead Records. This series includes source image material, client work files, correspondence, and work samples. Work files can contain project sample boards, print layout sheets, and her design-related resume and business cards. Burkhart also designed cover art for some of her ex-husband Jozef van Wissem's music albums, of which there are proofs and CDs represented in this series. Her promotional fliers, advertisements, and album cover artwork for the Dutch East India Trading and Homestead Records during the 1980s are also in this series. Various other completed client samples in this series include advertisements, brochures, and magazine layout pages, which illustrate the breadth of her clientele, from jewelry companies to recording studios. She also worked on a number of book cover designs, including Country Herbs and American Country Living: The Ultimate Lifestyle Compendium. Copies of those books are in this series to fully represent her work, along with layout boards. There are also cover design work samples for Burkhart's own novel, From Under the 8-Ball, published in 1985.
  - Book Layout Boards -- Schism, American Country Living, and Other Clients, 1980s, 1991-1992, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Country Herbs and American Country Living: The Ultimate Lifestyle Compendium, 1991-1992 (Box 30)
  - Client Projects -- Homestead Records and Dutch East India Trading, 1986-1987, undated (Box 25, Folder 9, Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Design Work -- Related Resumes, circa 1986-1993 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Graphic Art Client Projects, 1987, undated (Box 25, Folder 11, Box 44, Folder 4-5)
  - Client Project -- Julia Morgan Book, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Client Project -- Lost and Found, circa 1991 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Blank Invoice Sheets, 1991, 1993, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Thread Waxing Space -- Poster With Artists and Writers Listed, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Client Project -- Jozef van Wissem CD Cover -- Layout, circa 2000 (Box 26, Folder 3, Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Burkhart Business Cards and Negative, Layout, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Layout for The Tekas Horn-O-Matic, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Junkie Layout, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Source Materials, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - "The Look of Los Angeles" Section, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Imagine a Future Peace? -- Poster, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Negatives of Posters, Stuff, and Items for Sale, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - "Living in the Police State" and "Miller: Merchandise Pricing and Strategy", undated (Box 27, Folder Unknown)
  - Layout Board -- "Nuclear Threats to Human Survival", undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Series V. Teaching, 1988-2018; 2.10 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes.; 487.4 Megabytes in 127 computer files.
  Burkhart has been a professor at New York University and similar arts-related institutions teaching courses often themed around issues of art, sex, activism, and feminism. This series contains support material for specific classes as well as files on the application and administration of her various appointments, dating from the late 1980s to the mid-2010s. Class titles including Drawing I and II; Sex and Contemporary Visual Art; Art and Activism; and Introduction to Critical Theory. Documentation related to these classes includes course descriptions, syllabi, reading lists, notes, student correspondence, and images and lists of artworks used as visual aids during lectures. A significant amount of paper and electronic files in this series relate to Burkhart's course Medusa's Laugh: Contemporary Feminist Concepts and Visual Culture dating from 2003 to 2010, and includes readings, syllabi, lecture notes, and reading questions.
  Files related to the administration of her teaching positions contain lists of courses taught in previous years, and correspondence referring to applications to various institutions including New York University, Columbia University, and School of Visual Arts. Application files include course descriptions, references, resumes, and images of her work. This series also includes a small collection of identification cards from various institutions where she taught, and teaching philosophy statements.
  - "The Discourse of Others: A Personal, Theoretical, and Historical Critique" -- Workshop Brochure, Fall 1988 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - "Approach to the Fragmentary: A Conceptual Approach to College" -- Brochure, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - "Discourse of Others" -- Workshop, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Reference Lists, and Teaching Philosophy Statements, 1990-1998, 2000-2017 (Box 26, Folder 9-10)
  - Class Readings, circa 1990, circa 1996, undated (Box 26, Folder 11-13, Box 31, Folder 1-2)
  - Drawing I and II, Spring 1992 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Teaching Notes, 1993-1994, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Letters for Visual Arts Presentations, 1993-1996 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Teaching Job References, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence--from Students, 1994-1999 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Identification Cards, 1994-2015 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - School of Visual Arts -- Application Letter, Lecture Notes, Syllabus, 1996, 2012
  - San Francisco Art Institute -- Notes and Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Drawing I and II -- Syllabi, 1998, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Identity Politics and Aesthetic Expression -- Reading List, Course Proposal, and Notes, 1999-2000, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Sex and Contemporary Visual Art -- Syllabi, 2000-2011 (Box 31, Folder 13, Box 32, Folder 1-5)
  - Contemporary Art, 1976-2001 -- Syllabus and Reading Course Pack, Spring 2001 (Box 31, Folder 11-12)
  - Helene Cixous Lecture -- Notes and Related, 2001, 2006, 2010
  - New York University -- List of Classes, Payroll Files, Correspondence, 2002, 2010-2014
  - Medusa's Laugh: Contemporary Feminist Concepts and Visual Culture -- Readings, Syllabi, Lecture Notes, Reading Questions, 2003-2010, undated (Box 32, Folder 6-8, Box 33, Folder 1-4)
  - Lecture Notes, circa 2003-2018 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Art and Activism -- Syllabus and Notes, Fall 2004 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Art and Activism -- Readings, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Art and Activism -- Course Description, 2006
  - Images -- Class-related and Student Works, 2007-2013
  - Sex and Contemporary Culture -- Syllabi and Exam Questions, 2010-2014
  - Dream Courses Descriptions, 2011, 2014
  - Columbia University -- Application Letter, Supporting Documents, 2011-2012
  - Sex and Contemporary Art -- Syllabus, Description, and Readings, 2011-2013 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Sex and Contemporary Art -- Syllabi and Readings, 2012-2015 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Lecture -- "My Work", 2012
  - CUNY Talk -- Notes, 2013
  - List of New York University Classes Taught (2005-2012) and Related, 2013 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Bard College -- Application Letter, Dream Course Descriptions, 2014
  - Introduction to Critical Theory -- Readings, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Painting III and IV -- Syllabus, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Teaching Philosophy Statement, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate Seminar -- Syllabus, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Advanced Painting -- Syllabus and Reading List, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Notes, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Visual Culture -- List and Topics, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Sex Quiz, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Teaching Slides, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Interdisciplinary Art in Amsterdam -- Class Proposal, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Series VI. Personal, 1969-2013; 7.75 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes, 1 record carton, 2 oversize flat boxes, and 1 flat-file folder.; 135.1 Megabytes in 185 computer files.; 5 audiocassettes; 1 videocassettes (vhs)
  This series contains personal material in paper and electronic form, containing correspondence, photographs, astrological readings, and school ephemera, as well as musical mix tapes and audio correspondence to a friend. Print and digital images include pets, travel, friends, ex-husband Jozef van Wissem, professional portraits of Burkhart, gallery and museum events, and interior images of her apartments/studios in both Amsterdam and New York. Her correspondence dates from the 1970s to the 2010s, with friends, romantic partners, and fellow artists. Martinsburg High School and Shepherd College ephemera includes a yearbook, graduation announcement, and class notes. Ephemera from CalArts, where she studied art in the 1980s, includes a graduation announcement and various student publications containing her artwork and writings. Other personal items in this series include address books, published interview profiles on Burkhart, pet passports and related, and astrological readings and recordings. Photographs and clippings from Burkhart's wedding ceremony/performance piece with Jozef van Wissem are in this series. Video recordings and further documentation of the performance piece can be found in Series I.
  - Childhood Poem, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Photograph Album, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Martinsburg High School -- Yearbook, Graduation Invite, and Diploma, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 16-17)
  - Correspondence, 1970s-1980s (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, 1990s-2000s (Box 35, Folder 3-6, Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1994-2011
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 36, Folder 2-4)
  - Shepherd College -- Class and Personal Notes, 1976-1979 (Box 36, Folder 5-6, Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Dave (David) Cunningham -- Letters, Photographs, and Slides, 1980-1991 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Photographs -- Burkhart, Ex-Husband Jozef van Wissem, and Friends, 1980s-2000s (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
  - CalArts -- Student Publications and Graduation Announcement, 1981-1985, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 3-6)
  - "Hiroshima / Nagasaki. Whatever this Shit is. Bad. Awful", 1982-04-17 (Box 45, Audiocassette 467.0009)
  - Film by Paul Richmond, The Organization, 1984 (Box 45, Vhs 467.0016)
  - "60s to 80s Garage, Various, and Supremes. Totally Bitchen", 1986-09-28 (Box 45, Audiocassette 467.0014)
  - Pet Passports and Other Related Documentation, 1988-2013 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Autograph Book, 1989-1993 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Calendar and Planning Book, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Address Books and Contact Cards, 1990s, undated (Box 37, Folder 10-12)
  - Interviews and Quotes, 1990-2007 (Box 38, Folder 1, Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Wuthering Heights -- Gift, Book Inscribed by Burkhart's Mother, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - "Astrology Reading with Lexa", 1994-06-22 (Box 45, Audiocassette 467.0013)
  - Burkhart Business Cards, Identification, and Membership Cards, 1994, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Burkhart and Jozef van Wissem Wedding and Performance Piece -- Photographs and Clipping, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Lists -- Burkhart Ephemera and Books, 1996-2012
  - Astrological Chart Readings, 1998-2014 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Images -- Burkhart Portraits, Events, Friends, and Pets, 2007-2014
  - Income Spreadsheet, Deductions, Receipt Lists, 2009, 2011
  - Images -- Amsterdam Street Festival and Jamaica Trip, 2011-2014
  - Burkhart-Designed Party Invitation and Holiday Card, undated (Box 38, Folder 6-7)
  - Notes and Notebook, undated (Box 38, Folder 8-9)
  - Monique Safford Hand colored Prints, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Book Recommendation List from Artist John Baldessari, undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Handwritten Collage and Images, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Oversized Section of White Paper Containing Messages and Signatures, undated (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - "Fabulous Animal and Country Songs", undated (Box 45, Audiocassette 467.0003)
  - "Dear Diane / Dear Signora Diane", undated (Box 45, Audiocassette 467.0012)
- Series VII. Grace Knipe Papers, 1908-1996; 2.25 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes, and one 1/2 manuscript box.
  The Grace Knipe Papers were accumulated by her niece Kathe Burkhart and include Knipe's personal correspondence, diaries, notebooks, writings, and childhood ephemera, dating from the early 1900s to the 1990s. There is a small amount of early childhood ephemera including early 1900s school notes, as well as early poems and stories written sporadically from 1914 to 1977. Knipe's personal diaries date from 1929 to 1948 and are entered mostly in mini monthly journal books which typically contain daily appointments, family activities, work, national news, and the weather. This series also includes books and notes kept while Knipe participated in a Christian women's group through her church. This series contains a photograph of Knipe at 100 years old and obituaries for her husband William in 1959, and herself in 1996. There is also correspondence from neice Kathe Burkhart and also Knipe's sister dating from the 1970s to the 1980s. Burkhart wrote a book, Between the Lines (published in 2006), which was inspired by letters found after her aunt's death that were from Kate Gibson during the 1920s and 1930s. They appeared to have a close friendship and the letters often included family and friend news as well as events in their daily lives, while Grace worked outside the home in an office, and Kate lived in her family home and dealt with chronic illness.
  - Early Childhood Notebook, circa 1908 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - School Notebook with Exercises and Writings, 1914 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Writings, 1914, 1938, circa 1977, undated (Box 39, Folder 3-6)
  - Devotions Book, 1922 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Letters from Kate Gibson and Others, December 1927- April 1954 (Box 39, Folder 8-9, Box 40, Folder 1-5)
  - Diaries, January 1929-January 1948 (Box 40, Folder 6-8, Box 41, Folder 1-6)
  - Inscribed Bible, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Notepad -- Diary Entries and Expenses for Trip, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Mother Annie's Funeral Booklet, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Notebook, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Grace and William Knipe Obituaries, 1959, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Letters with Niece Kathe Burkhart, 1963-1989 (Box 42, Folder 5-7)
  - Scrapbook, 1975, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Photograph -- Knipe at 100 Years Old, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Notes -- Church Meetings, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Notebooks with Shorthand Notes, undated (Box 43, Folder 3-4)
- Series VIII. Journals, Datebooks, and Diaries, 1966-2016; 9.75 Linear Feet in 19 and 1/2 manuscript boxes.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access is restricted to researchers until the donor is deceased.
  This series contains journals, notebooks, diaries, and datebooks dating from the 1960s to the 2010s. Burkhart's early notebooks from the 1960s to the 1980s contain her thoughts and feelings growing up in West Virginia as a teen and young adult navigating high school and college, and also include poetry, notes to boyfriends, as well as her thoughts on artworks, college class notes, and projects. Later writings were often kept in appointment books, and entries were frequently a mixture of personal and professional thoughts, including studio notes, project ideas, travel plans, finances, relationship issues, poetry, and personal goals. These books are presently not available to researchers.
  - Journals and Diaries, 1966, 1971-1972 (Box 47, Folder 1-9)
  - Journals and Diaries, 1972-1977 (Box 48, Folder 1-9)
  - Journals and Diaries, 1977-1980 (Box 49, Folder 1-8)
  - Journals and Diaries, 1980-1983 (Box 50, Folder 1-8)
  - Journals and Diaries, 1983-1985 (Box 51, Folder 1-6)
  - Journals and Diaries, August 1985-April 1989 (Box 52, Folder 1-6)
  - Journals and Diaries, May 1989-January 1991 (Box 53, Folder 1-6)
  - Journals and Diaries, February 1991-March 1993 (Box 54, Folder 1-5)
  - Journals and Diaries, April 1994-1996 (Box 55, Folder 1-5)
  - Journals and Diaries, September 1996-June 1999 (Box 56, Folder 1-5)
  - Journals and Diaries, June 1999-May 2003 (Box 57, Folder 1-6)
  - Journals and Diaries, July 2003-April 2007 (Box 58, Folder 1-5)
  - Journals and Diaries, 2006-2010 (Box 59, Folder 1-7)
  - Journals and Diaries, 2008-2011 (Box 60, Folder 1-9)
  - Journals and Diaries, December 2011-February 2014 (Box 61, Folder 1-6)
  - Journals and Diaries, 2013-undated (Box 62, Folder 1-6)
  - Appointment Books, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Appointment Books, 1987-1991 (Box 63, Folder 1-4)
  - Appointment Books, 1992-1997 (Box 64, Folder 1-5)
  - Appointment Books, 1998-2010 (Box 65, Folder 1-4)
  - Appointment Books, 2010, 2012, 2015-2016 (Box 66, Folder 1-2)